http://www.2020seedlabs.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
We are committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your
personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”). As part of this commitment, our
privacy policy governs our actions as they relate to the collection, use and disclosure of
Personal Information. Our privacy policy is based upon the values set by the Canadian
Standards Association’s Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information and
Canada’s Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.
1. Introduction
We are responsible for maintaining and protecting the Personal Information under our
control. We have designated an individual or individuals who is/are responsible for
compliance with our privacy policy.
2. Identifying Purposes
We collect, use and disclose Personal Information to provide you with the product or service
you have requested, to manage and develop our business and operations, to meet legal
and regulatory requirements and to offer you additional products and services we believe
you might be interested in. The purposes for which we collect Personal Information will be
identified before or at the time we collect the information. In certain circumstances, the
purposes for which information is collected may be clear, and consent may be implied, such
as where your name, address and payment information is provided as part of the order
process.
3. Consent
Knowledge and consent are required for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal
Information except where required or permitted by law. Providing us with your Personal
Information is always your choice. However, your decision not to provide certain information
may limit our ability to provide you with our products or services. We will not require you to
consent to the collection, use, or disclosure of information as a condition to the supply of a
product or service, except as required to be able to supply the product or service. You may
withdraw consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable
notice.
4. Limiting Collection
The Personal Information collected will be limited to those details necessary for the
purposes identified by us. With your consent, we may collect Personal Information from you
in person, over the telephone or by corresponding with you via mail, facsimile, or the
Internet.
5. Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention
Personal Information may only be used or disclosed for the purpose for which it was
collected unless you have otherwise consented, or when it is required or permitted by law.
Personal
Information will only be retained for the period of time required to fulfill the purpose for which
we collected it or as may be required by law.
6. Accuracy
Personal Information will be maintained in as accurate, complete and up-to-date form as is
necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is to be used.
7. Safeguarding Customer Information
Personal Information will be protected by security safeguards that are appropriate to the
sensitivity level of the information. We take all reasonable precautions to protect your
Personal Information from any loss or unauthorized use, access or disclosure.
8. Openness
We will make information available to you about our policies and practices with respect to
the management of your Personal Information.
9. Customer Access
Upon request, you will be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of your Personal
Information, and will be given access to it. You may verify the accuracy and completeness
of your Personal Information, and may request that it be amended, if appropriate. However,
in certain circumstances permitted by law, we will not disclose certain information to you.
For example, we may not disclose information relating to you if other individuals are
referenced or if there are legal, security or commercial proprietary restrictions.
10. Handling Customer Complaints and Suggestions
You may direct any questions or enquiries with respect to our privacy policy or our practices
by contacting us at support@2020seedlabs.ca
Additional Information
Cookies
A cookie is a small computer file or piece of information that may be stored in your
computer’s hard drive when you visit our websites. We may use cookies to improve our
website’s functionality and in some cases, to provide visitors with a customized online
experience.
Cookies are widely used and most web browsers are configured initially to accept cookies
automatically. You may change your Internet browser settings to prevent your computer
from accepting cookies or to notify you when you receive a cookie so that you may decline
its acceptance. Please note, however, if you disable cookies, you may not experience
optimal performance of our website.
Other Websites
Our website may contain links to other third party sites that are not governed by this privacy
policy. Although we endeavour to only link to sites with high privacy standards, our privacy
policy will no longer apply once you leave our website. Additionally, we are not responsible
for the privacy practices employed by third party websites. Therefore, we suggest that you
examine the privacy statements of those sites to learn how your information may be
collected, used, shared and disclosed.
We are a global provider of superior seed testing services that includes all aspects of purity, germination and seed health.
We are accredited by the Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA), Canadian Seed Institute (CSI), ISO 9001 certified and the only private lab in Canada accredited by the International Seed Testing Association (ISTA).
ABOUT 20/20Who We Are
History of 20/20
Our Qualifications
Our Goals
News & Learning Centre
Contact Us
SERVICES WE OFFERSend Us a Test Sample
Seed Testing
®™ Trademarks of AM Royalties Limited Partnership used under license by LoyaltyOne, Co. and 20/20 Seed Labs. Inc.
Copyright © 2019 20/20 Seed Labs Inc. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
